<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter version="5.0" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
         xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
         xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
         xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"
         xmlns:m="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"
         xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
         xmlns:db="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
  <title>Overview</title>

  <section>
    <title>Product Introduction</title>

    <para>eformsign is an electronic document solution that allows anyone to
    easily create electronic documents from paper documents and utilize
    various data stored in electronic documents. You can easily create
    electronic documents by uploading your PDF files onto eformsign and
    converting the files to electronic forms via eformsign's Web Form Designer
    feature. You can also create electronic forms by using eformsign's add-in
    feature embedded in Microsoft Office (named <emphasis role="bold">Form
    builder</emphasis> or <emphasis role="bold">OZ in Office</emphasis>). The
    Form builder feature allows anyone who knows how to use the Microsoft
    Office Suite to easily convert existing documents to electronic
    forms.</para>

    <para>eformsign allows you to create a workflow for each template
    according to your company's business process. You can flexibly set a
    document signing process for internal documents requiring approvals as
    well as for external documents such as contracts, agreements, and
    applications. Furthermore, detailed configurations such as notifications
    and required input fields can be set for each workflow step or recipient,
    and the progress status of documents is logged as history. Moreover, an
    audit trail certificate is provided for the prevention of document forgery
    and falsification.</para>

    <para>eformsign also provides a bulk send feature, by which users can
    create and send multiple documents at once and can minimize repetitive
    input with auto-fill feature. Also, by adding and configuring custom
    fields, fields in documents such as company information, group and member
    information, recent input value, and date can be automatically filled in.
    Furthermore, eformsign allows users to easily manage companies' members
    and their permissions, configure detailed notifications settings for
    documents, and manage and utilize data entered in documents by extracting
    input data.</para>

    <figure>
      <title>Key Features</title>

      <mediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="resources/main_feature.png" width="800"/>
        </imageobject>
      </mediaobject>
    </figure>

    <para>The eformsign solution also provides a digital signature feature
    which allows you to sign e-signatures on electronic documents.</para>

    <para>A digital signature is a signature in electronic form that replaces
    the traditional wet-ink signature. Just as when signing a signature on
    paper, you need to prove that the signer is you and this is done by going
    through an identity verification step. Personal information such as email,
    social security number, password, phone number, certificate, etc. can be
    used to verify identity.</para>

    <para>Digital signatures have been legally binding in phases in the vast
    majority of countries around the world.</para>

    <para>eformsign’s e-signatures are legally binding for
    individual-individual and corporation-individual matters. As well, it
    provides various additional features for non-repudiation.</para>

    <note>
      <para>The following describes the legal effect of digital signatures of
      some regions.</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>South Korea: Digital signatures based on PKI standards have a
          strong legal status, and their legality is not discriminated against
          the wet-ink signatures. According to Section 3.3 of the Digital
          Signature Act, a digital signature other than a certified digital
          signature shall have such an effect of a signature, signature and
          seal, or name and seal, as is agreed between the parties
          concerned.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>USA: Under the "technologically neutral" principle, any
          preference to more sophisticated or more secure technologies such as
          PKI is not given. There are many cases of increasing the reliability
          of digital signatures through identity verification or
          authentication services.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>EU: Digital signatures are categorized into Qualified
          Electronic Signatures (QES), Advanced Electronic Signatures (AdES),
          and general Electronic signatures, and their legal status is applied
          accordingly, corresponding to the characteristics of each type of
          document.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para>Japan: With the existence of a Specified Authentication
          Services, a stronger legal effect is given to the digital signature
          authorized by the secretary of the state.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Basic Terms</title>

    <para>The following are some basic terms you should be familiar with
    before using eformsign.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Web Form Designer</emphasis></para>

        <para>Web form designer<indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Web form designer</primary>
          </indexterm> is a tool for quickly and easily creating electronic
        forms by uploading existing document files onto eformsign. You can
        create templates by adding components such as signature, text box, and
        check box to documents such as agreements, applications, and contracts
        in the PDF format. You can then create documents from templates and
        send them to recipients to be reviewed and signed.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Form Builder</emphasis></para>

        <para>Form builder<indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Form builder</primary>
          </indexterm> is a tool used to create electronic forms by converting
        Microsoft Office files such as applications, contracts, and agreements
        into electronic forms that contain components such as signature and
        text box. Form builder also uploads the converted electronic forms
        onto eformsign. Form builder is an Microsoft Office add-in, and it is
        shown as a ribbon menu which is called <emphasis role="bold">OZ in
        Office</emphasis>.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Dashboard</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Dashboard</primary>
          </indexterm>This is the main screen shown when logging into
        eformsign. You can access the sidebar menu by clicking the menu
        icon(<inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/menu_icon.png"/>
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject>) on the left side of the screen. Each menu may
        appear differently depending on the permissions you have. (The Company
        administrator can access all the menus.)</para>

        <figure>
          <title>eformsign Dashboard Screen</title>

          <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/dashboard.png" width="800"/>
            </imageobject>
          </mediaobject>
        </figure>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Templates</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Templates</primary>
          </indexterm>This is an electronic form that serves as a starting
        point for a new document. With a template, you can create many
        documents from it. You can create templates by converting existing
        Microsoft Office files using Form builder or by uploading PDF files
        directly onto eformsign.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">New document</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Documents</primary>
          </indexterm>New documents can be created by using templates in the
        <emphasis role="bold">New document</emphasis> menu. The number of
        documents created in eformsign refers to the documents created
        here.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Documents</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Documents</primary>
          </indexterm>This is a cloud space for storing and viewing documents.
        It consists of the following three spaces according to the document
        status:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">In progress:</emphasis><indexterm
                class="singular">
                <primary>In progress</primary>
              </indexterm> Shows the list of documents you have created or
            processed but are incomplete.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Action required:</emphasis><indexterm
                class="singular">
                <primary>Action required</primary>
              </indexterm> Shows the list of documents you have temporarily
            saved or documents that other members have requested to you to
            sign or approve.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Completed: </emphasis><indexterm
                class="singular">
                <primary>Completed</primary>
              </indexterm> Shows the list of all the completed documents you
            have created or participated in.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Workflow</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Workflow</primary>
          </indexterm>A workflow refers to the entire document process from
        when a document is created to when it is completed. Template managers
        can create the workflow steps for each template. All workflows have
        two default steps, <emphasis role="bold">Start –
        Complete</emphasis><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Start</primary>
          </indexterm><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Complete</primary>
          </indexterm>, and can add three more types of steps as shown
        below:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Approver: </emphasis><indexterm
                class="singular">
                <primary>Approver</primary>
              </indexterm>Step in which an approver can approve the document
            sent by the document creator.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Internal recipient:
            </emphasis><indexterm class="singular">
                <primary>Internal recipient</primary>
              </indexterm>Step in which an internal recipient, a member of the
            company, can review and sign the document sent by the document
            creator.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">External recipient:
            </emphasis><indexterm class="singular">
                <primary>External recipient</primary>
              </indexterm>Step in which a user who is not a member of the
            company can review and sign the document sent by the document
            creator (or the internal recipient).</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>

        <figure>
          <title>Workflow Steps</title>

          <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/workflow_new.png" width="400"/>
            </imageobject>
          </mediaobject>
        </figure>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Company Administrator</emphasis></para>

        <para><indexterm class="singular">
            <primary>Company Administrator</primary>
          </indexterm>The representative of a company and has full permission
        to use eformsign.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Template Management
        Permission</emphasis></para>

        <para>With this permission, a member can access the <emphasis
        role="bold">Manage templates</emphasis> menu and can manage templates.
        Managing templates includes creating, deploying, editing, and deleting
        the eformsign templates.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Document Management
        Permission</emphasis></para>

        <para>With this permission, a member can access the <emphasis
        role="bold">Manage documents</emphasis> menu to view the documents
        created from each template, approve documents requested to be voided,
        or permanently remove documents from the system. Note that the
        document management permission can be set for each separate
        template.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>eformsign Usage Flow</title>

    <para>To use eformsign, you can either upload a PDF file onto eformsign
    and create an electronic form online, or create a form using Microsoft
    Word, Excel, or PowerPoint and then upload it to eformsign.</para>

    <note>
      <para>Currently, the method of upload files and creating forms online
      only supports PDF files. Microsoft Office files, and image files such as
      JPG and PNG are planned to be supported in the near future.</para>
    </note>

    <section>
      <title>Using Web Form Designer</title>

      <para><indexterm class="singular">
          <primary>Web form designer</primary>
        </indexterm>You can create a template by uploading a document file(in
      the PDF format) on eformsign and then adding the components you want
      such as text, signature, and date onto the document. After adding
      components to the uploaded document, configure the template settings and
      deploy the template. You can configure the detailed template settings by
      going to the <emphasis role="bold">Manage templates</emphasis> menu &gt;
      selecting the template you want &gt; setting the <emphasis
      role="bold">General</emphasis>, <emphasis role="bold">Set
      permissions</emphasis>, <emphasis role="bold">Workflow</emphasis>,
      <emphasis role="bold">Field</emphasis>, and <emphasis
      role="bold">Notification settings</emphasis> tabs &gt; deploying the
      template. You can then go to the <emphasis role="bold">New
      document</emphasis> menu to create a document from a template you
      deployed and send it to recipients.</para>

      <figure>
        <title>Usage Flow of eformsign Using Web Form Designer</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/use_flow_web.png" width="800"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Using Form Builder</title>

      <para><indexterm class="singular">
          <primary>Form builder</primary>
        </indexterm>You can create a template by creating or opening a
      document file in Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and PowerPoint), and
      then using the ribbon menu (named <emphasis role="bold">OZ in
      Office</emphasis>) to add the components you want such as text,
      signature, and date onto the document. Then, you can upload the template
      you created onto eformsign by clicking the <emphasis
      role="bold">Upload</emphasis> button in the ribbon menu. After uploading
      the template, set the template settings and deploy the template. You can
      set the template settings by logging into the eformsign website, going
      to the <emphasis role="bold">Manage templates</emphasis> menu &gt;
      selecting the template you want &gt; setting the <emphasis
      role="bold">General</emphasis>, <emphasis role="bold">Set
      permissions</emphasis>, <emphasis role="bold">Workflow</emphasis>,
      <emphasis role="bold">Field</emphasis>, and <emphasis
      role="bold">Notification settings</emphasis> tabs &gt; deploying the
      template. You can then go to the <emphasis role="bold">New
      document</emphasis> menu to create a document from a template deployed
      and send it to recipients.</para>

      <figure>
        <title>Usage Flow of eformsign Using Form Builder</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/use_flow.png" width="800"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Minimum System Requirements</title>

      <para>The minimum system requirements for Form builder and eformsign are
      as follows:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para><emphasis role="bold">Form builder (OZ in
          Office)</emphasis></para>

          <itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">OS: </emphasis>Windows 7 and
              later</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">MS Office: </emphasis>Microsoft
              Office 2010 and later</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para><emphasis role="bold">eformsign and Web form
          designer</emphasis></para>

          <itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">OS:</emphasis> Windows 7 and later,
              OS X Mavericks and later</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Browser: </emphasis>Internet
              Explorer 11 and later, Chrome 49 and later, Safari 9 and
              later</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para><emphasis role="bold">Mobile OS:</emphasis> iOS: 6.1.6 and
              later, Android: 5.0 (Lollipop) and later</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist>

          <note>
            <para>Installing the mobile eformsign app is not a mandatory
            requirement to use eformsign.</para>
          </note>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Use Cases</title>

    <para>eformsign can be used for many different cases, including creating
    contract, agreement, and application forms. All documents are encrypted
    (AES-256 method) and stored in the PDF/A format, which is the
    international standard for long-term storage of documents.</para>

    <section>
      <title>Contract Forms</title>

      <para>Electronic documents can be used to sign various types of
      contracts including employment contracts, purchase/rental contracts,
      maintenance contracts, and franchising contracts. By using eformsign,
      you can record the history of contract processes, prevent the forgery of
      documents through audit trail certificates, and sign hundreds of
      contracts without meeting face-to-face with customers or contracting
      parties.</para>

      <para>The e-contract process using eformsign is as follows:</para>

      <figure>
        <title>E-Contract Process</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/contract_ex1.png" width="730"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Agreement Forms</title>

      <para>Electronic documents can be used to sign various types of
      agreements including privacy policy and consent forms, medical informed
      consent forms, parental consent forms, and sublease agreement forms. You
      can use various types of devices including smartphones, tablets, and
      computers to create and send thousands of agreement forms to recipients
      at once.</para>

      <para>The e-agreement process using eformsign is as follows:</para>

      <para><figure>
          <title>E-Agreement Process</title>

          <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/usecase-process.PNG" width="800"/>
            </imageobject>
          </mediaobject>
        </figure></para>
    </section>

    <section>
      <title>Application Forms</title>

      <para>Electronic documents can be used to sign various types of
      applications including application forms for registrations, quotations,
      medical treatments, and purchases. eformsign's workflow feature allows
      you to easily send application forms even when an application needs
      going through multiple departments in an organization as well as
      forwarding the document to the correct department. You can also send the
      copy of a completed document to the parties involved immediately after
      the document is completed.</para>

      <figure>
        <title>Example Workflow of an Application Form</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/workflow_ex1.png" width="400"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>

      <para>The e-application process using eformsign is as follows:</para>

      <figure>
        <title>E-Application Process</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/application_ex1.png" width="730"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
