<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter version="5.0" xml:id="createnew"
         xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
         xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
         xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
         xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"
         xmlns:m="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"
         xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
         xmlns:db="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
  <title>Creating documents</title>

  <section>
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para>Anyone can use eformsign to easily convert existing documents into
    electronic documents and then send them for signature. In eformsign, there
    are two ways to create and send documents. You can upload a file from your
    PC to eformsign, or use a existing template saved in eformsign.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">New from my file</emphasis>: You can
        upload your PDF file to create an electronic document and then send it
        to participants.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">New from template</emphasis>: You can use
        a template uploaded to eformsign to create documents. When you click
        this menu, templates created by the company administrator or members
        with template management permissions are displayed on the
        screen.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <note>
      <para>Templates can be created only by the company administrator or
      members with template management permission, and the templates on the
      screen are shown only to members who are given template usage permission
      for a given template.</para>

      <para>You can create a template using Web From Designer or Form Builder.
      For more information, refer to <xref linkend="template_wd"/> and <xref
      linkend="template_fb"/>.</para>
    </note>

    <important>
      <para>When creating a document with <emphasis role="bold">New from my
      file</emphasis>, you cannot save it as a template. For documents you
      plan on using frequently, it is recommended to register it as a
      template.</para>
    </important>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>New from my file</title>

    <para>You can upload a PDF file you want and then add fields (components)
    onto the document. Then, you can specify the participants that will fill
    in each component and enter the information of the document participants
    and reviewers, and then send the document.</para>

    <orderedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>Go to the <emphasis role="bold">New from my file</emphasis>
        menu.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-menu.png" width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Upload the PDF document file you want.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-uploadfile.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <note>
          <para>Only PDF files can be uploaded so far. Other file formats are
          planned to be supported in the future.</para>
        </note>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Add the <emphasis role="bold">document participants</emphasis>
        that will be participating in document creation and select their
        roles.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-participants-popup.png"
                       width="400"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <note>
          <para>You can add participants by clicking <emphasis role="bold">Add
          new participant</emphasis> and up to 30 can be added. Note that you
          can change, add, or delete participant information in the <emphasis
          role="bold">Add recipient</emphasis> step after the<emphasis
          role="bold"> Design form</emphasis> step.</para>
        </note>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Add the components each participant will fill in and then set
        component properties on the right.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-formdesign.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <para/>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>In the Add recipients step, you can add contact information such
        as email and phone number and set <emphasis role="bold">Recipient
        options</emphasis> for each participant.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-recipients.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <note>
          <para>There are two recipient types: reviewer and participant. The
          participants added in the Design form step are shown in the Add
          recipients step. You can enter the contact information of each
          recipient such as email. In the Add recipient screen, you can
          delete/add participants and reviewers and set detailed options for
          each recipient.</para>
        </note>

        <tip>
          <para><emphasis role="bold">The difference between participants and
          reviewers</emphasis></para>

          <para>Participants can fill in components such as signature and text
          on each document, but reviewers cannot fill in components and can
          only approve documents after reviewing them.</para>

          <para>However, if you set a component's <emphasis role="bold">Who
          can fill this out</emphasis> option to 'anyone', even reviewers can
          fill out the component.</para>

          <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-recipients-type.png"
                         width="400"/>
            </imageobject>
          </mediaobject>
        </tip>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Click the <emphasis role="bold">Options</emphasis> step to
        change the document title and select whether to timestamp the document
        when completed.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-option.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <note>
          <para>The above three steps are the steps you need to go through
          before creating a document. If you save the document as a draft
          before clicking the <emphasis role="bold">Start now</emphasis>
          button, the document is saved in <emphasis role="bold"><link
          linkend="drafts">Drafts</link></emphasis>, and the saved file can be
          opened again so that you can begin creating a document. To save a
          document as a draft, click the (<inlinemediaobject>
              <imageobject>
                <imagedata fileref="resources/menu_icon_3.png" width="20"/>
              </imageobject>
            </inlinemediaobject>) icon at the top right corner and then click
          <emphasis role="bold">Save as a draft</emphasis>.</para>

          <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-saveasdrafts.png"
                         width="200"/>
            </imageobject>
          </mediaobject>
        </note>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>When you are done with all the settings, click <emphasis
        role="bold">Start now</emphasis>.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-startfromnow.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>

        <caution>
          <para>A document is created once you click <emphasis
          role="bold">Start now</emphasis>, and it counts as a created
          document.</para>
        </caution>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>If you click the <emphasis role="bold">Send</emphasis> button
        after reviewing/filling in the document, then the document is sent to
        recipients.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newfrommyfile-startfromnow-send.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>
    </orderedlist>

    <para><emphasis role="bold">Add recipients &gt; Recipient
    options</emphasis></para>

    <para>In the <emphasis role="bold">Design form</emphasis> step or the
    <emphasis role="bold">Add recipients</emphasis> step, you can add
    participants who will receive the document.</para>

    <para>In the<emphasis role="bold"> Add recipients</emphasis> step, you can
    set detailed settings for each participant. Additionally, you can add or
    remove participants as well as adding reviewers who will review the
    document.</para>

    <para>You have to add the name of each participant and reviewer, and their
    email/ID. If a participant is a member of your company, you can select the
    member in the drop-down menu and import their member information stored in
    eformsign.</para>

    <para>The detail settings in <emphasis role="bold">Recipient
    options</emphasis> is displayed differently depending on whether the
    participant or reviewer is a member of your company or is an external
    recipient.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">When the recipient is a
        member</emphasis></para>

        <para>The email address and mobile number are automatically filled-in.
        You can select whether to send the document via email or
        mobile.</para>

        <caution>
          <para>When the mobile number option is selected, then the document
          will be sent via SMS and additional charges will occur.</para>
        </caution>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newformmyfile-recipientoption-member.png"
                       width="600"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">When the recipient is an external
        recipient</emphasis></para>

        <para>If the information you enter is not the same as the member
        information, then the recipient is recognized as an external
        recipient. This requires the below information to be filled in.</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Email/Mobile:</emphasis> You can
            select one of email and mobile, or both. If you select mobile,
            then you must enter the mobile number of the recipient.</para>

            <caution>
              <para>If you select mobile, then the document is sent via SMS
              and additional charges will apply per SMS.</para>
            </caution>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Document expiration: </emphasis>You
            can set the expiration period in which the external recipient can
            open and submit the document.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Set password: </emphasis>If you tick
            the Set password tick box, you can set the password required for
            the external password to open the document. For the password hint,
            you can set it to something the recipient will be able
            tell.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Require mobile verification to review
            documents: </emphasis>You can require mobile verification in order
            for the external recipient to open and fill-in the document. Extra
            charges apply.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para><emphasis role="bold">Require mobile verification to view
            completed documents: </emphasis>You can require mobile
            verification in order for the external recipient to open the
            completed document. Extra charges apply.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/newformmyfile-recipientoption-external.png"
                       width="400"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>New from template</title>

    <para>You can create and send documents whenever necessary by uploading
    frequently used forms and saving them as templates by adding workflows and
    other details.</para>

    <para>Templates can be created by using Web Form Designer or Form Builder.
    For more information, refer to <emphasis role="bold"><link
    linkend="template_wd">Web Form Designer </link></emphasis>and <emphasis
    role="bold"><link linkend="template_fb">Form
    Builder</link></emphasis>.</para>

    <note>
      <para>A document can only be created by members or groups that have been
      granted template usage permission (allows to create documents from the
      template) for a template by a member with template management permission
      for that template.</para>

      <para>A template is shown in the <emphasis role="bold">Manage
      templates</emphasis> page only to member/groups that have been granted
      template usage permission for that template.</para>
    </note>

    <orderedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>Click and go to <emphasis role="bold">New from
        template</emphasis> in the dashboard or the sidebar menu.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/menu-startfromtemplate.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Click the create icon(<inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata contentwidth="30" fileref="resources/create-icon.PNG"/>
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject>) of the template you want to create a document
        from.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/startfromtemplate-create.png"
                       width="700"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>If you create a document and then click the <emphasis
        role="bold">Complete</emphasis> or <emphasis role="bold">Request
        </emphasis>button on the top right corner, the document will proceed
        to the next step in the workflow. If you want to temporarily save the
        document as a draft before proceeding to the next step, click the
        <emphasis role="bold">Save as draft </emphasis>button to save.</para>

        <note>
          <para>The button may be displayed as<emphasis role="bold">
          Complete</emphasis> or <emphasis role="bold">Request</emphasis>,
          depending on the workflow set for the template.</para>
        </note>

        <important>
          <para>Documents saved when clicking the <emphasis role="bold">Save
          as draft</emphasis> when creating documents from templates can be
          found in the <emphasis role="bold">Action required</emphasis> page,
          not the <emphasis role="bold">Drafts</emphasis> page.</para>

          <para>To continue to create a document saved as a draft, click the
          <emphasis role="bold">Edit</emphasis> button in the <emphasis
          role="bold">Action required</emphasis> page.</para>
        </important>
      </listitem>
    </orderedlist>

    <para/>

    <section>
      <title>Send in bulk</title>

      <para>When creating a document from a template, you can use the
      <emphasis role="bold">Send in bulk</emphasis> feature to send a document
      to multiple recipients at once.</para>

      <note>
        <para>This feature requires either the company administrator or
        template usage permission.</para>
      </note>

      <para><emphasis role="bold">Send in bulk</emphasis></para>

      <para>1. Go to <emphasis role="bold">New document &gt; New from
      templat</emphasis><emphasis role="bold">e</emphasis>.</para>

      <para>2. Click the Send in bulk icon of the template you want to create
      a document from.</para>

      <figure>
        <title>Send in bulk icon</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/bulk-creation-icon.png" width="200"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>

      <para>3. Enter the values in the columns displayed on the screen.</para>

      <figure>
        <title>Send in bulk screen</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/bulk_create.png" width="800"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure>

      <note>
        <para>Each column of the table contains all the fields of a document.
        The IDs of components (which are fields in a template) are shown as
        the name of each column. The last row of the first column (No.)
        indicates the number of documents to be created.</para>

        <para>Tables are filled in a similar way as in Excel. You can
        double-click on each cell to enter a value and right-click on the
        mouse to add or delete columns. The value entered in a cell can be
        copied and pasted, and dragged to another cell.</para>
      </note>

      <para>4. Click the <emphasis role="bold">Preview</emphasis> button on
      the top right corner of the screen to view the documents you created and
      then click the <emphasis role="bold">Create</emphasis> button to send
      the documents.</para>

      <note>
        <para>If there is an external process step in a template, then the
        left area of the table is highlighted in blue. This area is for
        entering the external recipients’ names, emails, etc. Depending on the
        external process settings, there can be phone numbers, verification
        passwords, etc.</para>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="resources/bulk-creation-table-blue-section.png"
                       width="600"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </note>

      <para/>

      <tip>
        <para>If there is a component that is not shown in the <emphasis
        role="bold">Send in bulk</emphasis> screen, then the following must be
        checked.</para>

        <para>1. The components that cannot be entered in <emphasis
        role="bold">Send in bulk</emphasis>: camera, voice, and grouped radio
        components cannot be used in Send in bulk.</para>

        <para>2. Check whether the components are allowed access in Template
        settings. Only the components that are checked to be allowed access in
        <emphasis role="bold">Manage templates &gt; Template settings (⚙) &gt;
        Workflow settings</emphasis> are shown.</para>
      </tip>

      <para/>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
